Speiser Shumate Geoghan Krause & Rheingold Records
Speiser Shumate Geoghan Krause & Rheingold Records
- Case files
  - Wright et al. v. British Aircraft Corp and Braniff Airways (SA-393)
    - Evidence
      - Exhibits
        - 27, Vols. 1-2, 2 folders (Box 107)
        - 201-1 (Box 107)
        - 201-2 (Box 107)
        - 201-2, 3 folders (Box 108)
        - 202 (Box 108)
        - 203 (Box 108)
        - 204-6 (Box 108)
        - 205 (Box 108)
        - 206-2, 2 folders (Box 109)
        - 208-1 to 208-8, 8 folders (Box 109)
        - 208-10 (Box 109)
        - 209-1 and 209-2, 2 folders (Box 110)
        - 211-2 (Box 110)
        - 212 (Box 110)
        - 213-1 to 213-4, 4 folders (Box 110)
        - 214-38 (Box 110)
        - 215-1 and 215-2, 2 folders (Box 110)
        - 216 (Box 111)
        - B 201-2 to B 201-6, 5 folders (Box 111)
        - B 201-8 (Box 111)
        - B 201-10 (Box 111)
        - B 201-12 (Box 112)
        - B 201-14 to B 201-17, 4 folders (Box 112)
        - B 201-20 (Box 112)
        - B 201-23 (Box 112)
        - B 201-27 to B 201-29, 3 folders (Box 113)
        - B 201-32 (Box 113)
        - B 201-40 and B 201-41, 2 folders (Box 113)
        - B 202-1 (Box 113)
        - Second Series
          - 5A-S, 2 folders (Box 114)
          - 6,7A-H (Box 114)
          - 8A-C, 9A-C, 10 (Box 114)
          - 11A-B, 12B 12C-E (Box 114)
          - 13A (Box 114)
          - 13B (Box 114)
- Case files, 1972 additions
  - MA-119, Donna M. Barch v. Avco, Bendix & Paul G. Badgley Company
    - Pleadings and notes (Box 72-2)
  - SA-360, Eastern Airlines "Electra" Boston, Massachusetts crash
    - Depositions (Box 72-11)
  - SA-376, Pan American Airlines Boeing 707 Elkton, Maryland crash, 12/7/63
    - Depositions (Box 72-8)
  - SA-381, Eastern Airlines DC-7 Jones Beach, N.Y. crash, 2/8/64
    See also Case files: Craig v. Eastern Air Lines Inc., et al (SA-381)
    - Depositions (Box 72-9)
    - Exhibits and depositions (Box 72-6)
    - Exhibits and depositions (Box 72-7)
    - Law files (Box 72-10)
  - SA-386, United Airlines 727 Jet Lake Michigan crash, 8/16/65
    - Exhibits (Box 72-4)
  - SA-387, American Airlines 727 Jet Cincinnati Airport, Kentucky crash, 11/8/65
    - Depositions (Box 72-5)
    - Depositions (Box 72-13)
    - Exhibits (Box 72-3)
    - Notes, exhibits and depositions (Box 72-12)
    - Pleadings, correspondence and depositions (Box 72-1)
- Warsaw convention
  - Miscellaneous, 1957-1965 (Box 115)
  - Association of the Bar of the City of New York, 1958-1965 (Box 115)
  - Civil Aeronautics Board
    - Miscellaneous, 1947-1952 (Box 115)
    - Docket Entries re. Warsaw Convention (Box 115)
  - Correspondence
    - 1951 (Box 115)
    - 1954 (Box 115)
    - 1956-1957, 2 folders (Box 115)
    - 1959-1962, 5 folders (Box 115)
    - 1963-1966, 4 folders (Box 116)
  - Hague Protocol, 1955 (Box 116)
  - Interagency Group on International Aviation
    - Miscellaneous, 1961-1964 (Box 116)
    - Final Action, 1962 (Box 116)
    - Speiser's Notes, 1962 (Box 116)
  - International Civil Aviation Organization
    - Miscellaneous, 1953-1966 (Box 116)
    - Documentation, 1966 (Box 116)
    - Minutes, 1966 (Box 116)
  - Legislation, U. S. Congress
    - Bills and Resolutions, 1955-1965 (Box 117)
    - Reports and Hearings, 1963-1965 (Box 117)
  - Magazine separates, 1956-1965 (Box 117)
  - Memoranda, 1961-1966 (Box 117)
  - New York State Bar Association Aeronautics Committee, 1956-1959 (Box 117)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1956-1966 (Box 117)
  - Notes, undated (Box 117)
  - Press Releases, 1963-1966 (Box 117)
  - Related Cases
    - Miscellaneous, 1925-1952 (Box 117)
    - Holtzman v. Rusk, 1965 (Box 117)
    - Pierre v. Eastern Air Lines and Foxworth, 1957 (Box 117)
  - Rome Convention, 1952 (Box 118)
  - U.S. Senate Foreign Relations Committee Hearing, 1965 (Box 118)
  - Writings
    - Ereli, Elizer, "The Hague Protocol: An Abuse of Executive Discretion." UCLA Law Review, XI, 1964 (Box 118)
    - Gazdik, Julian G., "The Conflicts and State Obligations Under the Warsaw Convention, the Hague Protocol and the Guadalajara Convention," Journal of Air Law and Commerce (Box 118)
    - Karlin, Daniel, "Warsaw, Hague, the 88th Congress and Limited Damages in International Air Crashes," DePaul Law Review, 1962 (Box 118)
    - Kelner, Joseph and Harry A. Gair, Interview, undated (Box 118)
    - Kreindler, Lee S., "Interim Report on the Warsaw Convention", undated (Box 118)
    - Rottenberg, Simon, "Liability in Law and Economics", undated (Box 118)
    - Speiser, Stuart M.
      - "Can U.S. Airlines Afford the Warsaw Convention Any Longer?", 1963 (Box 118)
      - "Warsaw Convention and the American Lawyer," Harvard Law Review, XXIX, 1959 (Box 118)
    - Steuben, Norton, "Wrongful Death Actions Under the Warsaw Convention," Buffalo Law Review, 1962 (Box 118)
    - Wright, William B., "The Warsaw Convention's Damage Limitations," Cleveland-Marshall Law Review, 1957 (Box 118)